

PECE KATMEROSKI

Electrical engineer Electronics, automation and telecommunications

About Me

Graduate electrical engineer in electronics, automation and telecommunications, has been working dedicatedly and seriously for more than 10 years in this field, I carry out my tasks responsibly, I improve myself daily with the latest developments in technology, in the field of electronics, automation, programming, signal and data processing.

Professional Experience

Cable Network Operator INEL Kavadarci

2011 - Present

Key responsibilities:

- Operational Management
- Configure networks to ensure their smooth and reliable operation for fulfilling area objectives and processes.
- Monitor network performance and troubleshoot problem areas as needed.
- Oversee installation, configuration, maintenance, and troubleshooting of end user workstation hardware, software, and peripheral devices.
- Practice network asset management, including maintenance of network component inventory and related documentation and technical specifications information.
- Monitor and test network performance and provide network performance statistics and reports.
- Trouble ticket generation and response; carrier interface and escalations.
- Deployment and maintenance of network monitoring, analysis and reporting tools.
- Installation of network hardware and software.

Cable production factory FKN Negotino

2008 - 2011

Key responsibilities:

- Responsible in the cable construction department
- Involved in the automation and maintenance of the production process

Anhoch Computers-Skopje

2007 - 2008

Key responsibilities:

• servicing and maintenance of IT hardware and software

My Contact

voltasys@yahoo.com

(+389 71 250 798

0

st. Ilindenska 115-3/3 Kavadarci

Education Background

2003-2008

FACULTY OF ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING AND INFORMATION TECHNOLOGIES

"Ss.Cyril and Methodius" University in Skopje

Hard Skill

- Circuit Design and Analysis
- Digital Signal Processing (DSP)
- Programming and Software
- SQL DataBase
- Matlab
- C#, HTML, CSS, JS, Pyton
- Microcontrollers and Embedded Systems
- Creative thinking
- Power Systems and Distribution
- Analog Electronics
- Control Systems

Soft Skill

- Observation
- Decision makina
- Communication
- Multi-tasking
- Project management
- Innovation
- Attention to detail